<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LOG.M</string>
    <string name="memo_save">Save</string>
    <string name="memo_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="memo_create">Create</string>
    <string name="memo_modify">Modify</string>
    <string name="memo_delete">Delete Memo</string>
    <string name="memo_delete_all">Delete All Memos</string>
    <string name="memo_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="memo_app_info">App Info</string>
    <string name="memo_fix">Fix or Unfix Memo</string>
    <string name="memo_widget">Add Widget</string>
    <string name="todo_title">Title</string>
    <string name="todo_content">Content</string>
    <string name="todo_time">Time</string>
    <string name="todo_alarm_10">Alarm in 10 Minutes</string>
    <string name="no_memo">No memo</string>
    <string name="sort_memo">Memo Sorting</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="check_fix">Do you want to fix this todo at the top?</string>
    <string name="fab_content_desc">Create a new Todo memo</string>
    <string name="fixed_icon_description">Fix Todo memo</string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">EXAMPLE</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="app_widget_description">This is an app widget description</string>

    <!-- MainActivity -->
    <string name="delete_all_memos_title">Delete All Memos</string>
    <string name="delete_all_memos_message">Are you sure you want to delete all memos? Once deleted, the memos cannot be recovered.</string>
    <string name="delete_all_memos_confirm">Yes</string>
    <string name="delete_all_memos_cancel">No</string>
    <string name="sort_by_latest">Latest</string>
    <string name="sort_alphabetically">Alphabetical</string>
    <string name="sort_by_creation_date">Creation date</string>

    <!-- Privacy Policy -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">Personal Information Collection and Use Purpose
The Memo app collects personal information from users to provide functions such as memo creation, saving, modification, deletion, and widget display. The personal information collected includes the following:

Title and content of memos created by users
Date and time when memos are created
Widget ID to display memos as a widget
The collected personal information is only used for the purposes of memo creation, saving, widget display, and other related purposes, and is not used for other purposes.

Retention and Use Period of Personal Information
The Memo app retains personal information of memos until users delete them. When a user deletes a memo, the personal information of that memo is immediately deleted.

Provision and Sharing of Personal Information
The Memo app does not provide or share users personal information with third parties or leak it outside without their consent. However, when required by applicable laws and regulations, information may be provided in accordance with such laws and regulations.

Technological, Administrative Measures for Personal Information Protection
The Memo app complies with related laws and regulations such as the Personal Information Protection Act and takes the following technological, administrative measures to securely protect users personal information:

Minimizes the number of personnel with access to personal information
Personal information inquiries related to using the Memo app can be made by contacting the following email address:
Email: noion0511@gmail.com</string>
</resources>